===================================================

    * [### Score My Resume
        
        Get a free expert resume review, instantly](https://resumeworded.com/score)
    * [### Targeted Resume
        
        Tailor your resume to a job description in seconds](https://resumeworded.com/target)
    * [### LinkedIn Review
        
        Get personalized feedback on your LinkedIn profile](https://resumeworded.com/linkedin-review)

Privacy Policy
--------------

#### Last Updated: July 10th 2024

#### **If you're busy, here's a summary of the most common questions. For more details, scroll down to read the full Privacy Policy.**

#### \- We **do not** sell your data or your information. This is against our privacy policy and we hate those tactics as much as you do.

#### \- We **protect your privacy** and any data you provide is solely used to provide the features available on this site (to provide your resume reviews, resume targeting reports, LinkedIn profile reviews and generated cover letters).

#### \- To delete your account for any reason, login and fill out the form [here](https://resumeworded.com/account-deletion-request). We'll process your deletion request in a few days.

#### \- Once you join Resume Worded, you may get periodic email about your resume review and other career insights. There is a link to unsubscribe at the bottom of every email - clicking it will instantly unsubscribe you.

#### \- If you have registered for an account via an Organization (e.g. a university or educational organization), your resumes and usage data are accessible by authorized individuals, such as Career Services teams or University Counselors

#### At Resume Worded we know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personal Information is being used online. This is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information in accordance with our website, Resume Worded. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE STOP USING OUR SITE AND/OR SERVICES IMMEDIATELY.

* * *

What data do we collect when you create an account?
---------------------------------------------------

#### When you create an account with us, we collect profile information such as your name and email address. This is to help improve your experience or to authenticate you as a registered user. In addition to this information that you submit on the website, we may also collect information such as your IP address, Internet browser details, bandwidth, Internet Service Provider and other information needed to provide you with access to Resume Worded and obtain analytics.  
  
To access some features on Resume Worded (specifically the Score My Resume resume analysis engine, Targeted Resume, LinkedIn Review profile analysis engine, and Resume Worded Pro Lines and Metrics), you must create an account by clicking on "Sign in with Google" or "Sign in with Facebook" or other similar registering options, if available. You understand that, by creating an account, we will be able to identify you by your registered profile. Our third-party vendors, including but not limited, to Paddle, might also ask for your credit card or Paypal details if you want to purchase our premium products, Resume Worded Pro or LinkedIn Review. We do not collect or use any payment information and we claim no responsibility or liability for payment transactions.

What data do we collect when you upload your resume?
----------------------------------------------------

#### To provide recommendations, analysis, scoring and feedback on your resume via the Score My Resume or Targeted Resume functionality, our engine parses your resume and identifies information that may include, but not limited to, your resume's sections, your email address, IP address, your resume's content / bullet points, and your language. We use this data solely for the purpose of providing resume suggestions and recommendations to you privately.

What data do we collect when you upload your LinkedIn profile?
--------------------------------------------------------------

#### To provide recommendations, analysis, scoring and feedback on your LinkedIn profile via the LinkedIn Review functionality, our engine parses your uploaded LinkedIn profile PDF and identifies information that may include, but not limited to, your profile's sections, your profile's content / bullet points, and your language. Note that this data is your LinkedIn public profile. We use this data solely for the purpose of providing suggestions and recommendations on your LinkedIn profile privately.

What data do we collect when you generate a cover letter?
---------------------------------------------------------

#### To provide an AI-generated cover letter, you will be asked for details that you would like to be included on the cover letter. This information may include, but not limited to, your resume, the job description you are applying for, and additional context you want included. We use this data solely for the purpose of generating a cover letter for you privately.

When do we collect information?
-------------------------------

#### In addition to the above cases, we collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site. e.g. Provide us with feedback on our products or services

Where can I find a list of Resume Worded's subprocessors?
---------------------------------------------------------

#### Here is a non-exclusive list of our subprocessors and what they are used for. This list is subject to change as our business evolves.  
Format is **Subprocessor - Nature of processing:**  
Amazon Web Services - Storage and archival of Resume Worded user data and metadata.  
Vultr - Storage and archival of Resume Worded data and metadata.  
Digital Ocean - Storage and archival of Resume Worded data and metadata.  
Google - Authentication, tracking.  
Help Scout - Customer support help desk.  
Qwary - Customer support forms.  
Postmark - Email delivery services for communications to data exporter personnel involved in the data exporter-data importer relationship.  
Facebook - Authentication.  
OpenAI - Powering AI-enhanced writing features such as "Magic Write" and AI cover letter generator.  
Beehiiv - Sending our Coached email series and newsletters.  

May I opt out of Resume Worded Communications?
----------------------------------------------

#### Yes, you may opt out by clicking the Unsubscribe button at the bottom of every email. You can also email Resume Worded's Data Protection Officer by contacting [\[email protected\]](https://resumeworded.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Can I update or delete my personal data?
----------------------------------------

#### You have certain rights in relation to your Personally Identifiable Information. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information and confirm that it remains correct and up-to-date or choose whether or not you wish to receive material from us by Unsubscribing to our email list(s) (via the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email) or emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://resumeworded.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  
If you would like further information in relation to your rights or would like to exercise any of them, you may also contact us via [\[email protected\]](https://resumeworded.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If you reside or are located in the EEA, you have the right to request that we:  
  
\- provide access to any Personally Identifiable Information we hold about you;  
\- prevent the processing of your Personally Identifiable Information for direct-marketing purposes;  
\- update any Personally Identifiable Information which is out of date or incorrect;  
\- delete any Personally Identifiable Information which we are holding about you;  
\- restrict the way that we process your Personally Identifiable Information;  
\- provide your Personally Identifiable Information to a third party provider of services; or  
\- provide you with a copy of any Personally Identifiable Information which we hold about you.  
\- We try to answer every email promptly where possible, and provide our response within the time period stated by applicable law. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within our databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain your Personally Identifiable Information. Please also note that certain Personally Identifiable Information may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances, which may include if we need to keep processing your Personally Identifiable Information to comply with a legal obligation.  
  
When you email us with a request, we may ask that you provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity.

Use of Artificial Intelligence (AI)
-----------------------------------

#### We offer AI-enhanced features like "Magic Write" and our AI cover letter generator to improve your experience. Here's how we ensure your data stays safe:  
  
1\. **Your Choice**: These AI features are optional to use. You decide if and when to use them.  
  
2\. **Data Protection**: When you use these features, we only process the data necessary to provide the service you've requested.  
  
3\. **Trusted Partner**: We use OpenAI's technology for these features. They've committed not to use any data sent through their API to train or improve their AI models.  
  
4\. **Limited Data Retention**: OpenAI only retains data briefly for abuse monitoring, then it's deleted.  
  
5\. **Extra Safeguards**: We've implemented additional measures to protect your data, including opting out of any data training programs.  
  
For more details on OpenAI's practices, you can check their [Privacy Policy](https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy).

How do we use your information?
-------------------------------

#### **To provide Personalised Resume Recommendations:**  
Information provided by you will be used for Resume Worded's Score My Resume component including but not limited to, resume scoring, analysis, suggestions for improvement, suggestions for resume lines and metrics, or for sending you confirmation/reminder emails relating to your resume review (e.g. link to your analysis).  
  
**To provide you with missing skills from the Job Description:**  
The job description and resume provided to Resume Worded's Targeted Resume component will be used for comparing the job description to the resume and providing suggestions for improvement.  
  
**To provide Personalised LinkedIn Profile Recommendations:**  
Information provided by you will be used for Resume Worded's LinkedIn Review component including but not limited to, profile scoring, analysis, suggestions for improvement, or for sending you confirmation/reminder emails relating to your profile review (e.g. link to your analysis).  
  
**To provide Suggested Resume Lines:**  
Information provided by you will be used to suggest to you related resume lines in our database.  
**Please note that we will never use your resume lines in our Free or Pro databases of resume lines. Content on your resume is solely used for the purpose of making personalised recommendations to you, and are private to you.**  
  
**To provide AI-Enhanced Features:**  
If you choose to use our AI-powered features like "Magic Write" or our AI cover letter generator, we process your input data to provide personalized recommendations and content. This is done securely through OpenAI's API, with strict privacy measures in place. The use of these features is optional.  
  
**To securely authenticate you:**  
We use your profile information that you provided when you created an account to authenticate you and enable you to access our Premium services (Resume Worded Pro, LinkedIn Review) and your personalised resume report(s).  
  
**Service communications:**  
We may use your contact email for limited purposes, including but not limited to notification emails (e.g. such as when your resume review is ready, reminder emails, and feedback emails). If you have opted in to receive marketing material, we may send you an email for feedback purposes or product updates.  
  
We also may use this information to communicate with you through email, notices etc. posted on the Site, and other means accessible through the Services, to advise you about how to utilize Resume Worded, new features, updates, and key product information that will allow you to make better use of our Services;  
  
You can opt in or out of this at anytime via the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email. You agree that we may use this information for such communication with you.  
  
**Coached Email Series:**  
If you've opted in, we use your email address to send our Coached email series with career insights. You can easily unsubscribe at any time.  
  
**Improve our Services:**  
We may use your contact information for limited purposes, including but not limited to feedback purposes or our newsletter. We also may use this information to communicate with you through email, notices etc. posted on the Site, and other means accessible through the Services, to advise you about how to utilize Resume Worded, new features, updates, and general tips; You can opt in or out of this via the sign up form. You agree that we may use this information for such communication with you.  
  
**Customer Service / Support:**  
When you contact our customer support, we collect information such as your email address and your query. We use this information to be able to contact you and solve your query. We use this information to track potential problems and trends and customize our support responses to serve you better. Our customer support will endeavour to request or review only such information that is necessary to assist in your query or provide any other technical help you may require.  
  
**Third Party Services:**  
We may employ or engage third party companies (e.g. Help Scout) and individuals to facilitate support, investigation, review, promotion and advancement of our Site and/or Services. Additionally, we may use third party vendors (e.g. Paddle) and hosting partners to provide the necessary content, hardware, software, networking, storage and related technology required to run the Site and/or Services. These third parties are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations consistent with this Policy and have limited access to your information, meant only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are committed to not disclose or use it for any other purposes.  
  
**Payment:**  
When you pay for our premium services (Resume Worded Pro, LinkedIn Review), our third party payment processor may store data such as your name and email address to send you a payment receipt or other notifications. As stated above, this third party are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations consistent with this Policy and have limited access to your information, meant only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are committed to not disclose or use it for any other purposes.

#### Yes. Your resume and your resume review generated by Score My Resume and/or Targeted Resume is private to you. We use the data solely for:  
(a) providing resume line suggestions  
(b) providing feedback on your resume  
(c) providing general suggestions for improvement (e.g. missing keywords or skills)  
  
Note that if you have registered via an Organization (e.g. a university, or you used an organization code provided by your organization), your resume and usage data can also be accessed via authorized individuals, including but not limited to, Career Services teams, University Counselors, and Project Managers of the engagement.  
  
We may occasionally use anonymized, aggregated data to improve our analysis engine. This data cannot be used to identify you.  
  
We never use your resume's content in our tools or services beyond providing personalized recommendations to you.  
  
If you'd like us to delete your resume and associated files from our servers, please email us at support\[at\]resumeworded.com, and we'll delete your information within 48 hours.

Is my LinkedIn Profile private?
-------------------------------

#### Yes. Your resume and your profile feedback generated by LinkedIn Review is private to you, and as described, we use the data solely for:  
(a) providing a score on your profile  
(a) providing feedback on your profile  
(c) providing general suggestions for improvement  
  
Note that if you have registered via an Organization (e.g. a university, or you used an organization code provided by your organization), your resume and usage data can also be accessed via authorized individuals, including but not limited to, Career Services teams, University Counselors, and Project Managers of the engagement.  
  
We may occasionally use your data to improve the effectiveness of our analysis engine ('LinkedIn Review'), which is then also used on an anonymized, aggregated basis.  
  
In its aggregated form, data will not constitute Personal Data for the purposes of the GDPR as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. This information is strictly for analytics purposes and to help us improve the features and quality of our product. Such anonymized data will have all direct personal identifiers removed such as name, ID numbers, date of birth, demographic information, geolocation information, etc. We may share aggregated information that includes non-identifying information with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling. Furthermore, we agree not to attempt to re-identify anonymized data. Users of the Site and/or Services shall not be entitled to any compensation stemming from the use of such aggregated or anonymized information.  
  
Please note that we will never use your profile content in our Free or Pro databases of resume lines. Content on your LinkedIn profile is solely used for the purpose of making personalised recommendations to you, and are private to you.  
  
If you would like us to delete your resume and/or associated resume files from our servers, please email us at contact \[at\] resumeworded.com and we will delete your information from our servers within 48 hours.

How do we protect your information?
-----------------------------------

#### Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning.  
  
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
  
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.  
  
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider (Paddle or Stripe) and are not stored or processed on our servers.

Data aggregation
----------------

#### We may collect information about your use of Resume Worded, which is then also used on an anonymized, aggregated basis. This information is strictly for analytics purposes and to help us improve the features and quality of our Site and Service. Such anonymized data will have all direct personal identifiers removed such as name, ID numbers, date of birth, demographic information, geolocation information etc. We may share aggregated information that includes non-identifying information with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling. Furthermore, we agree not to attempt to re-identify anonymized data. Users shall not be entitled to any compensation stemming from the use of such aggregated or anonymized information.

Your choices
------------

#### **Option for Information Removal and Opt-Out**  
We may use your personal information to communicate with you through email, notices posted on Resume Worded, and other means accessible through our products, to offer you products and/or services. If you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, you may opt-out by unsubscribing from the communication or by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://resumeworded.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  
  
**Rights to Access, Correct, or Delete Your Information, and Closing Your Account**  
You have the right to access, change or correct your individual profile information, i.e. your Personal Data, with respect to your account. You can do so by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://resumeworded.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We reserve the right to take appropriate steps to authenticate your identity before providing access and to deny requests.  
  
If you wish to delete your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at contact \[at\] resumeworded.com. Kindly note that doing so may result in your not being able to access or receive certain services.

Do we use 'cookies'?
--------------------

#### Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computerâ€™s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the siteâ€™s or service providerâ€™s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They can be used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
  
If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

Third-party disclosure
----------------------

#### We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.  
  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third-party links
-----------------

#### Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
  
We have implemented the following:  
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.  
  
Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

California Online Privacy Protection Act
----------------------------------------

#### CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at:  
http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf  
  
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.  
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:  
      • On our Privacy Policy Page  
You can change your personal information:  
      • By logging in to your account  
      • Others  

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
----------------------------------------------

#### We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.  

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
----------------------------------------------------

#### It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking  

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
----------------------------------------------

#### When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.  

\- CAN-SPAM Act -
-----------------

#### The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. We collect your email address in order to market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to you after the original transaction has occurred.  
To be accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:  
\* NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses  
\* Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way  
\* Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters  
\* Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
\* Honour opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly  
\* Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email  
  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.  

\- Contacting Us -
------------------

#### If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please send an e-mail to  
support {at} resumeworded.com.

Get the job you deserve, faster.

Improve your resume  
  
Write your resume  

Optimize your career  

Get to know us  

© 2024 Resume Worded. All rights reserved.
